    <article id="10" date="2016-11-09">
        <header>Teacher comments on partially-completed unit planners for ePortfolios</header>
        <div name="desc">
            <p>Access to the teacher feedback on partially-completed unit planners for ePortfolios is now available. Teachers 
               are encouraged to complete the questionnaire on the quality of the partially-completed unit planners... 
            </p>
        </div>
        <div name="content">
            <p><strong>Access to the <a href="http://ibo.keysurvey2.com/f/1076569/1409/" target="_blank">teacher feedback 
               on partially-completed unit planners for ePortfolios</a> is now available.</strong>
            </p>
            <p>Teachers are encouraged to complete the questionnaire on the quality of the partially-completed unit planners. 
               All comments are carefully considered during the appropriate grade award meeting and are also useful for teams 
               preparing future unit planners. 
            </p>    
            <p>Feedback should be submitted no later than 20 November 2016.    
            </p>
        </div>
    </article>

    <article id="9" date="2016-11-09">
        <header>Teacher comments on MYP on-screen examinations</header>
        <div name="desc">
            <p>Access to the teacher feedback on MYP on-screen examinations 2016 is now available. Teachers are encouraged
               to complete the questionnaire on the quality of the on-screen examinations...
            </p>
        </div>
        <div name="content">
            <p><strong>Access to the <a href="http://ibo.keysurvey2.com/f/1076567/10fe/" target="_blank">teacher feedback on 
                MYP on-screen examinations 2016</a> is now available.</strong>
            </p>
            <p>Teachers are encouraged to complete the questionnaire on the quality of the on-screen examinations. All comments 
                are carefully considered during the appropriate grade award meeting and are also useful for teams preparing 
                future unit planners. 
            </p>    
            <p>Feedback should be submitted no later than 28 days after the examination.    
            </p>
        </div>
    </article>

    <article id="8" date="2016-11-09">
        <header>Report published on the May 2016 eAssessment</header>
        <div name="desc">
            <p>Find a full overview of the first MYP exam session, from candidate results and user feedback on technology 
               to opinions from examiners and schools...
            </p>
        </div>
        <div name="content">
            <p><strong>Find a <a href="m_0_mypxx_sur-nc16_1611_1_e.pdf" data-template="app:data-link" target="_blank">full 
               overview</a> of the first MYP exam session, from candidate results and user feedback on technology to opinions 
               from examiners and schools.</strong>
            </p>
            <p>This resource was updated on 4 November.    
            </p>
        </div>
    </article>

    <article id="7" date="2016-11-09">
        <header>MYP coordinator’s notes: November 2016</header>
        <div name="desc">
            <p>The <i>MYP Coordinator's notes:</i> November 2016 are now available in English, French and Spanish...
            </p>
        </div>
        <div name="content">
            <p><strong>The <i>MYP Coordinator's notes:</i> November 2016 are now available in English, French and Spanish.</strong>
            </p>
            <p>If MYP coordinators and teachers have any questions regarding either the content or technical 
               aspects of the notes, please contact <a href="mailto:ibid@ibo.org">ibid@ibo.org</a>.
            </p>
            <p>This resource was updated on 3 November.
            </p>
        </div>
    </article>

